<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>

<title>ROC RSS FEED</title>
<link>http://www.ropclub.com/</link>
<description>This is my rss 2 feed description</description>
<language>en-us</language>

<item>
<title>Reality Opportunity Club</title> 
<link>http://www.ropclub.com/index.php</link>
<description>The best part of this concept, REALITY OPPORTUNITY CLUB (ROC) is that you do not have to do anything different from what you have been doing till now. All you are required to do is to get your registration through our site www.ropclub.com free of cost(if you have any member distributer to refer you) and use ROC products</description> 
</item>
<item>
<title>About Us</title> 
<link>http://www.ropclub.com/roc-aboutus.php</link>
<description>It is anchored by an extra ordinary force of its beckoning and ever growing Real-Member-Distributors. The Chief Navigator and Captain of this dream-ship is a stalwart in Direct Marketing business and United Customer's Programme (UCP), who excelled in this avenue for the last few years.</description> 
</item>
<item>
<title>Our Mission and Vision</title> 
<link>http://www.ropclub.com/roc-mission.php</link>
<description>To reach out the horizon of a customer controlled market, where exploitation by unwanted middlemen and misdirecting advertisements are avoided or curbed. The customers get bespoke products and the Member-Distributors get their due benefits for linking ROC products.
Our India is a country of more than 100 Crores people, of which 80% are in the village. Their life style has to be uplifted and refurbished to the standard that of developed countries. Lot of self-less and voluntary efforts are required to educate, nurture and nourish them and make them aware of the need of the time.
ROC is an Endeavour to that goal.</description> 
</item>
<item>
<title>Business Plan</title> 
<link>http://www.ropclub.com/roc-businessplan.php</link>
<description>After using the product and feeling satisfied with quality and concept you can share your views with your friends and relatives. This way they will also start using the products and so on. Thus the ROC does not require any advertisement or middlemen for selling its products. The amount saved will be distributed between you and the people who associate to the company because of you. Day by day as your group will expand your income will also increase.</description> 
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
